const dayTwentyThreeQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "Who is the person that will receive the least punishment, among the dwellers of Hell fire that his shoes will be heated by fire and his brain will be boiling?",
    options: [
      "Abu Lahab",
      "Abu Jahl",
      "Abu Luhluhati Almajusiy",
      "Abu Talib",
      "Ubayi bn Khalaf",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the ruling on visiting a Soothsayer, merely asking him something without believing him?",
    options: [
      "Disbelief in Allaah",
      "Major Shirk",
      "It takes one outside the fold of Islam",
      "Allaah will not accept his/her Salat for 40 days",
      "It is permissible",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the ruling on visiting a Soothsayer, asking him something and believing him?",
    options: [
      "Disbelief in Allaah",
      "Major Shirk",
      "It takes one outside the fold of Islam",
      "Allaah will not accept his/her Salat for 40 days",
      "It is permissible",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Two conditions for worship of a Muslim to be accepted are …………. and……………",
    options: [
      "sincerity and belief",
      "sincerity and hope",
      "sincerity and in accordance with Sunnah of Muhammad SAW",
      "Islam and sincerity",
      "sincerity and hope",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Conditions of Taobah (repentance) that has nothing to do with the rights of another person are ……. ",
    options: ["six", "five", "four", "three", "two"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Conditions of Taobah (repentance) that has to do with the rights of another person are ……. ",
    options: ["six", "five", "four", "three", "two"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Is it right to start greeting Non-Muslims by saying: Assalam ‘alaik?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Is the real name of the Angel of Death Azarail?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Do we truly have Waliy (Holy man), today, among Non-Muslim and hypocrites?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was first known with Ta’teel (denial of Allah’s attribute)?",
    options: [
      "‘Abdullah bn Saba’",
      "Wasil bn ‘Ata’",
      "‘Amr bn Umayd",
      "Al Ja’du bn Dirham",
      "Ma’badu Aljuhani bn Khalid",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Highness of Allaah (‘Uluwu) is divided in to two; highness of ……and……",
    options: [
      "names and attributes",
      "attributes and action",
      "essence and attributes",
      "names and essence",
      "action and essence",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Is it possible for man to be afflicted by “the eye” (evil eye)?",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Masih Dajjal will come out, for how long will he live on earth?",
    options: ["One year", "forty days", "thirty days", "seven days", "one day"],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "With relevance to the most accepted view, the first man to reject destiny was ……………",
    options: [
      "‘Abdullah bn Saba’",
      "Wasil bn ‘Ata’",
      "‘Amr bn Umayd",
      "Al Ja’du bn Dirham",
      "Ma’badu Aljuhani bn Khalid",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Allah created stars for three things, what are they?",
    options: [
      "To beautify the night sky, projectiles against the devils and guidance for the wayfarer at night",
      "For calculation, guidance and beautification of sky",
      "For calculation, determination of future occurrence and guidance",
      "For calculation, determination of future occurrence and beautification of sky",
      "To beautify the night sky, determination of future occurrence and guidance for the wayfarer at night",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
];
export default dayTwentyThreeQuestions;
